<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on El Indalo</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on El Indalo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 09:58:08 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Immigration for Brits - still count as an EU Citizen</title>
      <link>/posts/immigration-still-as-eu-citizen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 09:58:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/immigration-still-as-eu-citizen/</guid>
      <description>A recent visit to &amp;ldquo;Extranjería&amp;rdquo; (Immigration) showed that there nothing for the British immigrant to do at present to regularise their position. The blue EU &amp;ldquo;tarjeta de residencia&amp;rdquo; residents card provided to the EU citizen continues to be valid.
I was assured that it remains valid, that I have no need to renew it nor even have it re-issued with my current address. They have so far no knowledge of what will happen or when this will be announced, and in typical Spanish fashion, &amp;ldquo;don&amp;rsquo;t worry!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>High Quality BBC Radio in Spain</title>
      <link>/posts/high-quality-bbc-radio-in-spain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 09:48:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/high-quality-bbc-radio-in-spain/</guid>
      <description>When you are abroad the BBC limit the radio you can receive via iPlayer to lower bandwidth streams. However every BBC radio station has a high quality stream which is only available in the UK. Even there, these are not widely advertised.
I managed to get mine going in the south of Spain, and I think these will work anywhere in the world.
A VPN or tunnel will generally not work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>El Indalo</title>
      <link>/posts/el-indalo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 09:36:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/el-indalo/</guid>
      <description>El Indalo comes from neolithic cave paintings discovered in Vélez-Rubio in the north of the province of Almería in the nineteenth century. In the twentieth century it was adopted by a group of intellectuals and artists who became known as the Indalino movement. This group was led by the painter Jésus de Perceval, who has a street in the capital named after him. They saw their emblem as a little man holding up a rainbow, meant to symbolise a pact between man and the gods to avoid future floods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another substantial increase in minimum wage</title>
      <link>/posts/minimum-wage-increased-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 09:58:08 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/minimum-wage-increased-again/</guid>
      <description>The coalition government increased the minimum wage for full time employees to 950 euros with 14 payments per year. This builds on the 22.3% increase from 735 to 900 euros brought in by the socialist government en funciones last year.
Podemos wanted Sanchez to put it straight up from 735 to 1000 euros last year. But Sanchez was more cautious, realising that this would cause a backlash from businesses affected by the sudden increase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January in Almeria</title>
      <link>/posts/january-in-almeria/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 09:27:45 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/january-in-almeria/</guid>
      <description>January 2020 is cool and damp in the capital. In the mountains it&amp;rsquo;s cold and there&amp;rsquo;s snow at the top of the higher ones.
This attracted a lot of city dwellers out to the sierra at the weekend, with the intention of seeing snow and doing a few selfies! Calar Alto is a favourite for this, an added benefit being the domes of the space observatory as a nice background. Unfortunately for many families the road up from Gérgal was closed to traffic all weekend, there was just too much snow and ice for safety.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>